(hip-hop bass thudding)
(sirens wailing faintly)
(hip-hop music over speakers)
Damn, man.
It's hot as hell in there.
Don't be breaks, man.
You know, we could, um--
we could do some
instrumental shit,
you know,
like a Kendrick album.
I know the recorder
a little bit, so, like,
we could do a song
like "Pussy Relevance."
You can come in like...
* Pussy relevance
-both: * So intelligent
-And then I can come in like...
* Do, do-do-do,
do, do *
* Do-do-do-do-do,
do, do, do *
* Do-do-do, do, do
And you can be like,
"Bye, everybody,"
-Like, "I'm gonna take a break."
-(coughing)
(laughter)
(laughing)
(sighs)
'Sup, guys?
I'm Zan.
Hey!
Paper Boi.
Good shit, homey.
You blowing up right now,
my nigga.
Yeah,
I don't know you.
But I'm still your nigga,
believe me.
Shit,
are you even black?
Of course I am.
You want a hat, Paper Boi?
Nah, we're--
we're good, man.
All right.
Peep this.
(phone clicks)
Is that a meme
depicting what happens to you
or to bae when
they scroll through the DMs?
(tsks)
Man, whatever.
I got those likes.
Guess who saw someone
throw up on the booth?
Hey!
Back the fuck off
Paper Boi, man!
-The fuck, man?
-Whoa.
Oh.
My bad.
Is this your boy?
'Sup, man?
I'm Zan.
You want a hat?
Nigga.
-Yeah.
-Right on.
Let me get one
for the 'gram.
(hoverboard whirring)
Oh, yeah.
(camera shutter clicking)
And one more for Snapchat.
All right, man.
That's enough.
What?
Are you sure?
I'm a photographer, man.
I took this.
Oh, it's your face
next to a butt.
Wait, I forget.
What's your email?
I never gave it to you.
It's cool, just...
just take my phone number, man.
Yeah, yeah,
I'll text you mine.
Maybe we can collab
on a song or shirt.
Or sneakies.
Yo!
Me and my mans make
baby sneakers for adults.
We good, bro.
Take that over there.
Yeah, a'ight.
I see you, then.
(hoverboard whirring)
(Xavier Wulf's
"Philosopher's Throne")
- * I pull off with my (...)
finna throw a fit *
- * Who? Who?
- * I pull up on a bitch
* I don't say shit,
she getting in *
* But I had to kick her out
* 'Cause I ain't
tell her ass to get in *
(electronic music slowly builds
over headphones)
*
Paper mail.
* Paper mail,
all about my paper mail *
(chewing)
Mm. Mm.
Breakfast cup.
You made that up.
Everything's made up,
nigga, stay woke.
Hey, man.
That dude from last night
talking shit.
What?
"Paper Boi,
who getting
"a lot of hype in the streets
for a possible
"involvement with a murder,
is, how you say,
not as talented
as people think."
That's a weird...
sentence.
(keys clacking rapidly)
Right, uh,
you ready to go?
-Yeah.
-Oh, also,
is it okay if I spend
the night over here again?
Wayne.
(hisses)
(cell phones ding)
Damn, bro,
you going off, ain't you?
-(keys clacking)
-Yep.
Yeah, man.
Don't bait this dude.
You'll just make it worse.
(keys clacking)
Hey!
(light thud)
You're gonna make it worse!
(keys clacking)
AIDS was invented to keep
Wilt Chamberlain from beating
Steve McQueen's sex record.
You know, by '69,
he was already
number three
on the all-time list.
By '71, he would have
beat that boy for sure.
I thought AIDS was made by the
government to kill homosexuals.
Oh, yeah, that too,
I mean, but...
Two for one.
Mm-hmm.
Who's Steve McQueen?
(scoffs)
The actor, man.
You know.
The King of Cool.
You know, guy from
The Sand Pebbles.
I don't know.
Man, most black people
don't know who Steve McQueen is.
Really?
Yeah, but I thought,
you know, that you'd be
into that kind of stuff,
but guess not.
But you know who
Steve McQueen is, though.
Yeah, well, I'm Nigerian.
Okay.
-(hip-hop music)
-Yo, man, the club,
it's so lit,
it's so lit up in here.
Yo, how you feeling?
Lit!
Ooh!
Yeah!
(Twitter app whistles)
(jazzy music)
Ah, recording all night
really paid off.
Oh, look, I found
all my mixtapes.
Let's put 'em back
where they belong.
(gas pump clicks)
(store entrance bell chimes)
(relaxed music over radio)
MAN: How much can I get
for this gun?
MAN: I need to get a copy of
your driver's license first.
MAN: That makes sense.
-All right, I'll see you.
-Good luck.
*
Yeah, what's up?
EARN: Yeah, um,
I got this phone, it's new.
I want to see how much
I could get for it.
MAN: I got to ask my boss.
EARN: Cool.
Uh, is it cool
if I have--
I have something of yours
while you have something of mine
like, like a driver's license
or something like that, just...
-(samurai sword resounds)
MAN: No.
Earn.
Yeah?
Earn!
What?
Get this sword.
Why?
We could trade up on it.
We get you a lot more money.
*
I really need this, man.
Well, if you need the money,
take the money.
I'm just saying
I can get you more.
*
MAN: $190.
Actually, let me
get this sword, man.
*
MAN: You want to swap it out?
-Yeah, I want to swap it out.
*
Hey, you know
who Steve McQueen is?
Yeah.
Would you know
who Steve McQueen was
if you didn't work here?
Black people don't know
who Steve McQueen is.
I keep that there
for protection.
If some dude come in here
asking about that poster,
I know he's trying to get me
to turn around so he can rob me.
Sign this.
*
Get you a receipt.
Thank you.
I wasn't trying to...
rob you.
-(hip-hop music)
-'Sup, guys?
It's your boy, Zan,
with another mixtape review.
If you like what you hear,
hit this Like button and
re-blog the fuck out of my ass!
Yeah!
(air horn blares)
Let's talk about
the current king of stan rap,
Paper Boi.
MAN: * Paper Boi, Paper Boi
ZAN: The first L this dude took
is naming himself Paper Boi
in the first place.
There's already
a rapper Paperboy.
He had that song "Ditty."
Or how about
this Paper Boi?
Also this
Papuh Boi too.
I mean, how am I
supposed to spell "failure"
when you're taking
all the Ls?
*
MAN: * Paper Boi, Paper Boi
* Always 'bout that paper,
boy *
This Paper Boi is hot.
This is the problem
with rap right now, man.
Every nigga can't sell drugs,
just like every nigga
can't rap.
But when you're out here
and you can't do both,
what the fuck
are you doing, bro?
(somber rock music)
I mean, really?
*
He is kind of funny.
What's his Twitter handle?
Man, shut up.
You told me to watch it.
*
Yo, is this nigga Indian?
I don't like Indian dudes
who say "nigga."
(pool balls clacking,
ball thuds)
It's just the Internet.
It doesn't matter.
Man, he out here saying
I can't rap and I don't move.
Man, that's disrespect.
You don't want people
to know you move.
-Trust me.
-I don't, man,
but I can't have people
out here talking shit.
He messin' with my
actual business, my life.
He don't even know
what he talkin' about, man.
Nobody checking
his credentials.
Why he get to attack mine?
Shit.
MAN:
* You walked into my life
He's one of these misguided
niggas who loves hip-hop.
No, he don't, man.
He out here selling T-shirts.
He exploiting it.
MAN: What he look like?
(inhales)
(scoffs)
I mean,
is he Dominican, man?
Like...
Somebody was in here
looking for you today,
waiting when I opened.
Really?
This dude?
No, he wasn't Dominican,
I don't think.
But he was different.
Shaved side of his head.
Pink jacket.
And he wasn't a friend.
Sitting in his car
when I opened up.
Dodge Challenger,
'70s, tan.
Cleaner than
the board of health.
I'll tell you,
smoking a Swisher
with no weed.
Guy gave me the creeps.
(Twitter app whistles)
*
Yo.
Zan going on now.
(scoffs)
*
(chuckling)
The fuck?
MAN: * Paper Boi, Paper Boi,
Paper Boi... *
What you think?
Bruh.
MAN: * Paper Boi, Paper Boi,
Paper Boi... *
-What you think?
-* I got--
-Bruh.
-Zan?
Nigga, I know that guy.
He used to come down
to the old place.
Word?
In fact, I think I know
where he works.
*
No.
(hip-hop bass thuds)
*
Do you know if you can
block someone on a flip phone?
Why?
'Cause that dude Zan
keeps mass-texting me
every party in Atlanta
and he keeps calling them
"movements"
and I fucking hate him.
Hmm.
Wasn't that dude, like,
half Chinese or something?
I don't know.
Probably.
He was pretty short.
Ni-i-ice!
Chinese people
are short
'cause of Genghis Khan.
-Look it up.
-In what?
The Racism Book?
(Keith Ape's "It G MA Remix"
playing over speaker)
Look, this dude
killed enough people
to lower the temperature
on Earth.
And if he conquered you
and you were bigger
than this wheel he had,
crrk, he'd kill you.
*
Is that true?
You don't think that
had an effect genetically?
Plus, Chinese people
don't like black people no way.
-Look it up.
-Again, where?
*
And he's not Chinese.
I'm not Chinese.
Wait right here, bro.
MAN: * Rambo, rambo, rambo
(machine gun fire)
* Rambo, rambo
* Bitch, I'm a zombie
(rapping in Korean)
(dice rattling)
* Camo down,
you know we going *
* Harder than a mutha,
mutha(bleep) ape *
-* Whoo
-(rapping in Korean)
*
He said meet him around back.
No, he didn't.
*
(man speaking foreign language)
(speaking foreign language,
crying)
(goat bleating)
(yelling in foreign language)
Oh, yay.
My man.
Thank you very much.
Yeah?
Brother.
Is he going
to get the money?
Uh...
Got to make a quick
trade up.
It's the last stop.
Come on, Barfight.
(dog growls and barks lightly)
(goats bleating)
(sirens wailing)
Hey, man.
Oh, hey,
what's up, man?
Nigga--
-We need to talk.
-Yeah, sure, we can talk.
I just gotta deliver this,
though, uh...
Ride with me.
We'll talk.
You coming, bro?
(engine turns over)
(sighs)
So what's up, man?
-You working on a mixtape?
-Look, man.
I don't know if you know
what's happening out here,
but this ain't no game,
a'ight?
I'm getting tired of niggas
online harassing me.
Ah, fan engagement.
No, man, you messin'
with my life, man.
This my job.
Helping us get money,
though.
Nigga!
There's no money
anywhere near rap.
Now, I know it look
fun and games on The Shade Room,
but...niggas die.
People are forgotten.
Shit is real.
Yo, can I use that?
Use what, man?
What you just said.
Like, if I was recording this,
could I use that?
Nigga, are you
recording me right now?
I record everything, man.
Everything's valuable
to someone.
Okay, so then you admit it.
You ain't no critic
or a photographer.
You--you like a salesman
or something.
What's the difference?
I mean,
it's all the game.
We're all just hustling.
You too.
'Cause I have to.
I scare people at ATMs,
boy.
So I have to rap.
I mean, that's what rap is--
making the best
out of a bad situation,
brother.
Right.
You're exploiting
your situation.
What?
You're exploiting
your situation to make rap,
and I'm exploiting you
exploiting that.
Money, bro.
(exhales)
Whatever, man.
I, like--I could say
some shit right now,
but I ain't trying to go off
on you with your son back there.
That's not my son.
That's my business partner.
We make Vine videos together.
Hos love this little nigga.
He just needs an edge.
We got a catch phrase, though.
Say it!
Sure I know, bitch!
Hmm.
Try the alt.
I...
(sustained bleep)
(bleep continues)
...on everybody face.
(chuckling)
Hmm?
Put your seat belt on,
Quentin.
(engine running)
(hip-hop bass thudding)
*
(brakes screech)
(gear clicks)
A'ight, let's do this,
Quentin.
Wait.
You got this kid
delivering your pizzas?
Word of mouth.
I'm watching him the whole time,
it's cool.
*
(knocks on door)
Wait--hold up, man.
Did he just get robbed,
man?
Shit is crazy, B.
(recording button dings)
*
(sighs)
(knocking on door)
QUENTIN: Give me the pizza.
Give me
(bleep) pizza back.
(bleep)
Give me...
Give me (bleep)
pizza back!
Give me the (bleep) money!
(bleep).
I know where you live!
-(insects chirping)
-(humming)
(engine shuts off)
(birds cawing and chirping)
Oh, come on,
come on, come on, buddy.
(sighs)
(dog panting)
How much we
getting for him?
Uh, about 2 to 4K.
Hell yeah.
Hell. Yeah.
Hey, hey.
Hey, D.
Ah,
here he blows.
Yeah.
So what you think?
Yeah, this a good dog.
Uh-huh.
Cool?
All right.
-Here you are.
-Good deal.
I'll catch you.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
(whispers)
Let's go, buddy.
Yes.
(exhales)
Hey, you going
to get the money?
Yeah.
Yeah, in September.
What?
Yeah, he's gonna take that
Cane Corso and breed it
with his other Cane Corso.
They're gonna have
Cane Corso puppies.
They gonna sell them pups
for 2K each.
And you get half.
Man, you 'bout to come up
off that phone, brother.
Are you joking?
No.
You all right,
brother?
No, no, I'm actually
kind of fucked.
Van needed that money.
My daughter needed
that money, okay?
Not in September,
but today.
Okay?
See, I'm poor, Darius.
And poor people
don't have time
for investments
because poor people
are too busy
trying not to be poor,
okay?
I need to eat today,
not in September.
Right, I asked you
at the pawn shop,
if you needed the money,
to take the money.
And you said you
wanted more money,
so I got you more money.
(birds chirping
and twittering)
Look.
Here, trade this in.
-No, it's cool, man--
-No, no, it's fine.
I'm just stressed.
I got a lot going on.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
I get a new one every month.
Make sure they ain't
tracking me.
Thank you.
We're friends now.
(car door thuds closed)
(birds chirping)
(Michael Kiwanuka's
"Home Again" plays)
*
KIWANUKA: * Born again,
born again *
*
* One day I know
* I'll feel strong again
* I lift my head
*
* Lost again,
lost again *
*
* One day I know
* Our paths
will cross again *
*
* Smile again,
smile again *
*
* One day I hope
* To make you smile again
* I won't hide
*
* Many times I've been told
* Speak your mind
* Just be bold
* So I close my eyes
* Won't look behind